{
    "subject": "resource/Bonerama",
    "predicate": "http://xmlns.com/foaf/0.1/name",
    "object": "Bonerama",
    "human_readable": "The name of Bonerama is Bonerama.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9645392894744873,
            "question": "What is the name of Bonerama?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.839862585067749,
            "question": "What is Bonerama known for musically?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7733350992202759,
            "question": "Who are the members of Bonerama?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6435315608978271,
            "question": "Where is Bonerama based?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5526163578033447,
            "question": "Is 'Bonerama' a musical group?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5382541418075562,
            "question": "Are there any famous songs by Bonerama?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4882776439189911,
            "question": "Is there a website dedicated to Bonerama?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4731583893299103,
            "question": "Does Bonerama have a specific genre?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.36548271775245667,
            "question": "Has Bonerama released any albums?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.34177446365356445,
            "question": "Has Bonerama won any awards?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The name of Bonerama is Bonerama.",
            "html": "dbpedia_9024_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Has Bonerama released any albums?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9024_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Does Bonerama have a specific genre?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9024_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is there a website dedicated to Bonerama?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9024_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9024_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9024_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9024_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9024_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9024_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9024_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9024_43.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9024_69.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9024_70.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9024_71.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "The triple to be evaluated is:\n\n\"Is the name of Bonerama 'Bonerama'?\"\n\nBased on the context information provided, here's my evaluation:\n\n* In multiple documents (14.txt, 26.txt, and 70.txt), the band is consistently referred to as \"Bonerama\".\n* The band's members, Mark Mullins and Craig Klein, are mentioned in several documents, but there is no mention of a different name for the band.\n* The descriptions of the band's music and style are consistent across the documents, but none suggest that the band has a different name.\n\nGiven this information, I conclude that:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe provided documents contain multiple mentions of the band \"Bonerama\" and provide details about its music, formation, and members. Therefore, the statement that the name of Bonerama is Bonerama is supported by the given context."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Most Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}